League of Women Voters of Albany County; Records apap128
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Study and Action, 1952-2000; 5; 7.14 cubic ft.
  - New York State Constitutional Convention Vote No Action Kit and League Position, 1997 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 18)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Copy of New York State Constitution, 1997 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 19)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, Newsletters, Pamphlets, News Clippings, 1997 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 20)
  - New York State Constitutional Convention, News Clippings, 1997 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 21)
  - Nuclear Medicine/ Low Level Radioactive Waste, 1988 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 22)
  - Pesticides, 1988-1990 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 23)
  - Pesticides, 1996-1997 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 24)
  - Population Coalition, 1997-1999 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 25)
  - Public Authorities, 1987 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 26)
  - Reapportionment, 1979; 1982 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 27)
  - Recycling, 1989 (Box 21 (5-Study and Action), Folder 28)
  - Recycling, 1989-1990 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 1)
  - Reproductive Choice, 1989-1990 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 2)
  - Reproductive Choice, 1993 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 3)
  - Self-Advocacy for Older Adults, 1977 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 4)
  - Self-Advocacy for New York's Citizens, 1978 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 5)
  - Self-Advocacy for New York's Citizens, 1980 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 6)
  - "Study and Action" Brochures by LWVAC, 1970-1993 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 7)
  - Task Force to Rethink LWVAC, 1998-1999 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 8)
  - Telephone Tree for Action, 1998-1999 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 9)
  - Term Limits, 1992; 1994 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 10)
  - United Nations, 1962-1966 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 11)
  - United States Congress Study, 1970-1971 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 12)
  - United States Congress Study, 1971 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 13)
  - United States Constitution, Interpretation, 1987 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 14)
  - U.S. Foreign Policy, Brochures and Correspondence, 1954; 1972-1973; 1979-1980; 1987 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 15)
  - Universal Health Care, 1989-1990 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 16)
  - Universal New York Health Care, 1989-1991 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 17)
  - Universal New York Health Care and Governor Cuomo's Town Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 18)
  - Urban Crisis Study, 1978-1979 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 19)
  - Waste Prevention Tool Kit, 1997 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 20)
  - Water Resources, 1963-1965; 1996 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 21)
  - Water Resources, Hudson-Mohawk Basin Study, 1966-1967 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 22)
  - Water Resources, Hudson-Mohawk Basin Study, 1968-1969 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 23)
  - Water Resources, Water Quality Survey, 1987 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 24)
  - Water Resources, Water Quality and Protection, 1990-1991; 1994 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 25)
  - Water Resources, Albany County Water Coordinating Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 26)
  - Water Resources, Albany County Water Coordinating Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 27)
  - Water Resources, Watersheds and Wetlands, 1995-1996 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 28)
  - Water Resources, Drinking Water, 1997 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 29)
  - Women and Social Policy, 1985-1986; 1990 (Box 22 (5-Study and Action), Folder 30)
  - Increase Your Citizen Power, Self-Advocacy Training, Undated (Box 40 (5-Study and Action), Folder 4)
  - Strengthening Women's Rights in Newly Independent States, Personal Notes and Planner, 1995 (Box 40 (5-Study and Action), Folder 5)
  - Water Resources, Proposition #1, 1963-1965 (Box 40 (5-Study and Action), Folder 6)
- Subject Files, 1942-2000; 6; 3.74 cubic ft.
  The Subject Files series is an arbitrary organization of materials collected by the LWVAC that are not related specifically to the functions of administration, voter service, or informing citizens about public policy issues. Included in this series are items from other organizations like the Citizen's Environmental Coalition and the Government Law Center; projects the LWVAC took part in like the Environmental Shopping Program (1990-1991) and Good Government Week (1976); convention materials from the state and national LWV; news clippings; and possible program items. Subjects including records produced by the LWVAC are history and anniversary campaigns, public relations, and sponsorship projects. The LWVAC sponsored women to visit the area for the LWV's Project Demokracia: Building Citizen Participation in Hungary (1994) and Strengthening Women's Rights in the Newly Independent States Internship Program (1995).
  - Albany County Opportunity Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Albany-Shaker Corridor Study by Capital District Transportation Authority, 1979 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Alternatives to Fluorocarbons Environmental Acceptability Study, 1991-1993 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Campaign for Fiscal Equity, 1997-1998 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Canal Revitalization Program, 1996 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Carrie Chapman Catt Memorial Fund, 1952-1962 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Citizen's Committee for Albany Public Schools, 1953-1955 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Citizen's Environmental Coalition, 1990-1992 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Citizen's View of '52, 1952 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Congressional Voting Record, 1985 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Council of Community Services, 1961; 1965; 1970 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Endocrine Disruptors Screening and Testing Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Energy, 1991-1992 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Environmental Advocates, 1997 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Environmental Defense Fund, 1997 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Environmental Groups, 1989-1992 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Environment, Self Help Program, 1992 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Environmental Shopping Program, 1990-1991 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Global Issues Discussion Group, 1998 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Global Warming, 1991-1992 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Good Government Week, 1976 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Government Law Center, 1994 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Guest Speakers, 1988-1991 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Guest Speakers, 1992-1995 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Hazardous Waste Management, 1987-1989 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Hazardous Waste Management, 1991 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - History, LWVAC, 1992-1995 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - History, 40th Anniversary of LWVAC, 1962 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - History, 50th Anniversary of LWVUS Campaign, 1970 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - History, 50th Anniversary of LWVUS, Campaign Memos and Newsletters, 1968-1971 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - History, 50th Anniversary of LWVNYS, 1968-1969 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - History, 50th Anniversary of LWVAC Committee Meetings and pamphlet drafts, 1970-1972 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - History, 50th Anniversary of LWVAC pamphlet, 1972 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - History, 50th and 55th Anniversary of LWVAC, skit, 1971; 1977 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - History, Members of LWVAC 25 years or more, 1975 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - History, 60th and 65th Anniversary of LWVUS, 1985 (Box 23 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - History, 70th Anniversary of LWVAC, Pamphlet, 1992 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - History, 75th Anniversary of LWVNYS, 1994 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - History, 75th Anniversary of LWVUS, Program, 1992-1995 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - History, 75th Anniversary of LWVUS, Contributions to American Communities, 1994-1995; 1997 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - History, 75th Anniversary History Project, 1993 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - History, 75th Anniversary Oral History Project, 1993 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - History, 75th Anniversary of LWVAC, 1997 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - History, Women's Suffrage, 1954; 1958; 1972-1976; 1980; 1994-1995 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Home Rule for Washington, D.C., Correspondence and News Clippings, 1965; 1978; 1980-1984; 1991 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Household Hazards, LWVAC Presentation, 1990 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Hudson River Estuary Management Plan, 1990 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Hudson River PCB's Reassessment, 2000 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Hudson River Valley Greenway, LWVAC Comment on Draft Study, 1990 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Land Conservation in New York State, 1990-1992 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Land Conservation in New York State, 1991 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - LWV Education Fund Projects, 1987-1988; 1990; 1993; 1995 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - LWV National Convention, 1958 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - LWV National Convention, 1962 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - LWV National Convention, 1964 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - LWV National Convention, 1966 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - LWV National Convention, 1968 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - LWV National Convention, 1980; 1984; 1986 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - LWV National Convention, 1988 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - LWV National Convention, 1990 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
  - LWV National Convention, 1994 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - LWV National Convention, 1998 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - LWV National Council, 1983 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - LWVNYS Council Kit, 1998 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - LWVNYS and The Foundation for Citizen Education, 1988-1995 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - LWVNYS Self Study, 1973 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - LWVNYS 13 State Council, 1962 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - LWVNYS State Convention, 1975 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - LWVNYS State Convention, 1995 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - LWVNYS State Convention, 1997 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - LWVNYS State Convention, 1999 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - LWV of Rensselaer County, 1996-1997 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - LWV Statement on the Death of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 1968 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - League of Women Voters Week, 1964; 1974 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Mediation Assistance Program, 1995 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Natural Resources, Environmental Conservation, 1997-1998 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - New Pioneers in the Capital District, 1953 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - News Clippings, 1965; 1968-1969; 1972-1979 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - News Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 24 (6-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - News Clippings, 1982-1986 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1986-1991 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1991 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1991-1993 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1995-1997 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1997-1999 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, Undated (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - New York State Americanization Project, 1954-1956 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1990 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - New York State Legislative Forum, 1997; 1999 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Non-Point Education for Municipal Officials, 1999 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Pesticides, Community Gardens, 1981; 1986-1987; 1990-1991 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Pesticides, Lawns, 1986-1987; 1989-1990 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Pesticides, NYCAP, 1989-1990 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Pesticides, NYCAP, 1990; 1991 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Port of Albany, 1959 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Press Packets, 1991-1992; 1994-1995 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Program Agendas, 1942-1954 (not inclusive) (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Program Planning, 1958; 1964; 1966-1969 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Program Planning, 1974-1980 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Program Planning, 1981-1986 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Program Planning, 1986-1988 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Program Planning, 1988-1990 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Program Planning, 1992-1995 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Program Planning, 1995-1998 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Project Demokracia, Building Citizen Participation in Hungary, Background Material, 1994 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Project Demokracia, Building Citizen Participation in Hungary, Correspondence, 1994 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Project Demokracia, Building Citizen Participation in Hungary, Proposal, 1994 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Public Relations, Guides, 1963; 1994-1995 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Public Relations, 1951-1953 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Public Relations, 1954-1956 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Public Relations, 1960-1964 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Public Relations, 1965-1969 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Public Relations, 1980; 1990-1995 (Box 25 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - School Buses, 1985 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Solid Waste Management, Plastics, 1988-1992 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Solid Waste Management, Plastics, 1989-1992 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Solid Waste Management, Toxins, 1987-1990 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Solid Waste Management, Waste Reduction, 1989-1991 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Solid Waste Management, Waste Reduction, 1990-1991 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Solid Waste Management, Work on Waste, 1988-1991 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Solid Waste Management, News Clippings, 1983-1992 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Strengthening Women's Rights in the Newly Independent States Internship Program, Application, 1995 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Strengthening Women's Rights in the Newly Independent States Internship Program, Proposal, 1995 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Strengthening Women's Rights in the Newly Independent States Internship Program, Background Material, 1995 (Box 26 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Strengthening Women's Rights in the Newly Independent States Internship Program, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Strengthening Women's Rights in the Newly Independent States Internship Program, Activities, 1995 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Strengthening Women's Rights in the Newly Independent States Internship Program, Final Report, 1996 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - T.V. Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - United States Bicentennial, 1975-1976 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - War Powers Act, Correspondence and News Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Welfare Reform in New York, Undated (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Westchester County Redistricting, 2001 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Wetlands, 1991 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Women and Equity, 1995 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Women's Interfaith Observance, 1981; 1984-1985 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Women in Politics, 1984 (Box 27 (6-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - LWV National Council, 1991 (Box 40 (6-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - New York State Legislative Session, 1997 (Box 40 (6-Subject Files), Folder 8)
- Publications, 1940-2001; 7; 7.77 cubic ft.
  This series includes League publications from the local, state, and national organizations. There is also material produced by other organizations that was collected by the LWVAC. There is a relatively comprehensive collection of the LWVAC newsletter The Active Voter, now known as Educate, Participate, Advocate, as well as newsletters from the state and national Leagues. Other publications by the LWVAC such as Voter's Guides, Household Hazards: A Guide to Detoxifying Your Home, and This is Albany County are included in Series 2, Series 3, and Series 4, respectively. Publications and other material by the state and national LWV include such items as brochures and pamphlets discussing public policy issues and citizen participation and board reports sent to the local Leagues. The series includes material produced by other organizations and is arranged alphabetically by subject. For example, there are a number of items relating to the New York State Constitutional Convention of 1967 and financing education. Materials in this part of the series, while not part of a particular study, may have been used as background material for some League studies found within the other series of this collection.
  - Albany County and Other County Branches of the LWV, 1944-2001; 7.1
    - The Active Voter, 1944-1946 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
    - The Active Voter, 1946-1947 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
    - The Active Voter, 1948-1949 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
    - The Active Voter, 1950-1951 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
    - The Active Voter, 1952-1953 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    - The Active Voter, 1954-1955 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
    - The Active Voter, 1956-1957 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
    - The Active Voter, 1959-1960 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
    - The Active Voter, 1961-1962 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - The Active Voter, 1963-1964 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
    - The Active Voter, 1965-1967 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
    - The Active Voter, 1968-1969 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
    - The Active Voter, 1970-1971 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
    - The Active Voter, 1972-1974 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
    - The Active Voter, 1975 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
    - The Active Voter, 1976 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
    - The Active Voter, 1977 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
    - The Active Voter, 1978 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 18)
    - The Active Voter, 1979 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 19)
    - The Active Voter, 1980 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 20)
    - The Active Voter, 1981 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 21)
    - The Active Voter, 1982 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 22)
    - The Active Voter, 1983 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 23)
    - The Active Voter, 1984 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 24)
    - The Active Voter, 1985; 1986 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 25)
    - The Active Voter, 1987 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 26)
    - The Active Voter, 1988; 1989 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Action in Albany: Legislative Priorities, 1978; 1982-1986; 1997 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Albany County Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 29-30)
    - California LWV Newsletters, 1955; 1998 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 1992 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 1993 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 1994 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 1995 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 1996 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 1997 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 1998 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 1999 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Educate, Participate, Advocate, 2001 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 40)
    - Minerals -- Foundations of Society, 1984 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Schenectady County "Who's Who," Schenectady County LWV, 1994-1995 (Box 28 (7-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Legislative News Service of the LWVNYS, 1964-1971; 1976-1977 (Box 40 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - New York State Voter, 1977-1999 (Oversized 3)
  - National LWV, 1940-2001; 7.2
    - League of Women Voters Educational Fund Blueprint for Clean Water, 1982 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 1)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Campaigning for Fair School Finance: Techniques that Work, 1978 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 2)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Changed Forever: The League of Women Voters and the Equal Rights Amendment, 1988 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 3)
    - League of Women Voters Educational Fund A Citizen's Guide to Electric Utilities, 1985 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 4)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Close-Up of Washington, 1958 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 5)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Coping With Conflict: Reproductive Choices and Community Conflict, 1986 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 6)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Crosscurrents: The Water We Drink, 1989 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 7)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Debates '84, 1984 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 8)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Election '84 Wrap Up, 1985 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 9)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Electoral Participation: Gateway to Democracy, 1986 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 10)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Energy Dilemmas and Energy Options, 1977 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 11)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Environment Brochures, 1959 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 12)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Fighting Hunger in Your Community: A Guide for the Development of Community Action Projects, 1990 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 13)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund, 1989-1992 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 14)
      Food Forum Education Project, America's Growing Dilemma: Pesticides in Food and Water, 1989 and Seeds of Tomorrow, 1992.
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund A Nuclear Power Primer: Issues for Citizens, 1982 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 15)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund The Nuclear Waste Primer: A Handbook for Citizens, 1980; 1985 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 16)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund Pay Equity: Issues and Answers, 1986 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 17)
    - League of Women Voters Education Fund "Pick a President", 1976 (Box 29 (7-Publications), Folder 18)